var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمَ",
        "answer": "the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "rootWordId": 227,
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīma",
        "frequency": 26,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " لَتَرَوُنَّ الْجَحِيمَ",
        "rootWord": "ج ح م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ج ح م",
        "waznEnglish": "(of) the blazing Fire",
        "waznTlit": "jīm ḥā mīm",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 26,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَرَوُنَّ",
        "answer": "Surely you will see",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "rootWordId": 523,
        "tlit": "latarawunna",
        "frequency": 328,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " لَتَرَوُنَّ الْجَحِيمَ",
        "rootWord": "ر أ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَءَا",
        "waznEnglish": "to see",
        "waznTlit": "raā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 271,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَرَوُنَّهَا",
        "answer": "surely you will see it",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "rootWordId": 523,
        "tlit": "latarawunnahā",
        "frequency": 328,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ لَتَرَوُنَّهَا عَيْنَ الْيَقِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ر أ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَءَا",
        "waznEnglish": "to see",
        "waznTlit": "raā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 271,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "زُرْتُمُ",
        "answer": "you visit",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 640,
        "tlit": "zur'tumu",
        "frequency": 6,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " حَتَّىٰ زُرْتُمُ الْمَقَابِرَ",
        "rootWord": "ز و ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "زُرْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to visit",
        "waznTlit": "zur",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتُسْأَلُنَّ",
        "answer": "surely you will be asked",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "rootWordId": 647,
        "tlit": "latus'alunna",
        "frequency": 129,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ لَتُسْأَلُنَّ يَوْمَئِذٍ عَنِ النَّعِيمِ",
        "rootWord": "س أ ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَأَلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to ask",
        "waznTlit": "sa-ala",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 106,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you will know",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "rootWordId": 1016,
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": 854,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " كَلَّا سَوْفَ تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَلِمَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to know",
        "waznTlit": "ʿalima",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 382,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you will know",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "rootWordId": 1016,
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": 854,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ كَلَّا سَوْفَ تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَلِمَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to know",
        "waznTlit": "ʿalima",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 382,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "rootWordId": 1016,
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": 854,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " كَلَّا لَوْ تَعْلَمُونَ عِلْمَ الْيَقِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَلِمَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to know",
        "waznTlit": "ʿalima",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 382,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمَ",
        "answer": "(with) a knowledge",
        "pcklId": "658",
        "rootWordId": 1016,
        "tlit": "ʿil'ma",
        "frequency": 854,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " كَلَّا لَوْ تَعْلَمُونَ عِلْمَ الْيَقِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عِلْم",
        "waznEnglish": "they know",
        "waznTlit": "ʿil'm",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 105,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(with the) eye",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "rootWordId": 1046,
        "tlit": "ʿayna",
        "frequency": 65,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ لَتَرَوُنَّهَا عَيْنَ الْيَقِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ع ي ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَيْن",
        "waznEnglish": "(having) beautiful eyes",
        "waznTlit": "ʿayn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 57,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَقَابِرَ",
        "answer": "the graves",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "rootWordId": 1171,
        "tlit": "l-maqābira",
        "frequency": 8,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " حَتَّىٰ زُرْتُمُ الْمَقَابِرَ",
        "rootWord": "ق ب ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَقَابِر",
        "waznEnglish": "and provides a grave for him",
        "waznTlit": "maqābir",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّكَاثُرُ",
        "answer": "the competition to increase",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "rootWordId": 1259,
        "tlit": "l-takāthuru",
        "frequency": 167,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " أَلْهَاكُمُ التَّكَاثُرُ",
        "rootWord": "ك ث ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَّكَاثُر",
        "waznEnglish": "much ",
        "waznTlit": "takāthur",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun (form III)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْهَاكُمُ",
        "answer": "Diverts you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 1355,
        "tlit": "alhākumu",
        "frequency": 16,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " أَلْهَاكُمُ التَّكَاثُرُ",
        "rootWord": "ل ه و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَلْهَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to distract, to divert",
        "waznTlit": "alhā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 4,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّعِيمِ",
        "answer": "the pleasures",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "rootWordId": 1492,
        "tlit": "l-naʿīmi",
        "frequency": 140,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ لَتُسْأَلُنَّ يَوْمَئِذٍ عَنِ النَّعِيمِ",
        "rootWord": "ن ع م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَعِيم",
        "waznEnglish": "then good",
        "waznTlit": "naʿīm",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 17,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَقِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) certainty",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "rootWordId": 1660,
        "tlit": "l-yaqīni",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " كَلَّا لَوْ تَعْلَمُونَ عِلْمَ الْيَقِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ي ق ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَقِين",
        "waznEnglish": "firmly believe",
        "waznTlit": "yaqīn",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 8,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَقِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) certainty",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "rootWordId": 1660,
        "tlit": "l-yaqīni",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 102,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ لَتَرَوُنَّهَا عَيْنَ الْيَقِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ي ق ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَقِين",
        "waznEnglish": "firmly believe",
        "waznTlit": "yaqīn",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 8,
        "hasRootWord": true
    }
]; 
export default words;